Kouki?
Come on!
Let's stay a bit more!
But it's almost bedtime.
I'm not sleepy at all!
Let's go, Kouki!
Let's go home.
I'll be with you in a bit.
Shall I take you somewhere fun?
Somewhere fun?
Is it okay if we go somewhere else first?
Sure...
Man, you're heavy!
Don't drop me!
Do you even have an aquarium?
Nah, but we have a bath!
You can't put it there!
When you get home, put it in a bucket of tap-water and flush it in the veranda.
What for?
Tap-water has chlorine in it.
All right! Come on!
Rin?
Hold still a sec.
Look.
Hey!
Let's go already!
Don't drop me!
Come on!
Here we are.
It's the river!
Wait for me!
I didn't know about this spot...
Is it Rin's first time here too?
Yes.
In fact, this is our first summer together.
It's too dark. I can't see anything.
Daikichi! Help!
C'mere c'mere...
Let's look there!
Wait up!
It's so late! Are we still doing something?
That sounds like someone I know.
All right, come with me, Kouki.
Good night.
G'night...
Good night!
Let's go too.
You've gotten taller, haven't you?
The way home